[{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678872005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":17996,"timeElapsed":95104},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678890848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":18837,"timeElapsed":113948},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678909834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":18979,"timeElapsed":132934},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678926774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":16936,"timeElapsed":149874},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678938994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":12216,"timeElapsed":162094},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":12370,"timeElapsed":174469},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5777,"timeElapsed":180254},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4403,"timeElapsed":184663},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678969160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7589,"timeElapsed":192260},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":19753,"timeElapsed":217755},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":14325,"timeElapsed":232085},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679023494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":14502,"timeElapsed":246593},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8399,"timeElapsed":254999},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":13363,"timeElapsed":268367},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":9090,"timeElapsed":277465},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679061115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6745,"timeElapsed":284215},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5955,"timeElapsed":290175},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6627,"timeElapsed":296807},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":15951,"timeElapsed":318893},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8801,"timeElapsed":327699},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":9567,"timeElapsed":337271},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7971,"timeElapsed":345247},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":9270,"timeElapsed":354521},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3875,"timeElapsed":358399},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679139935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4628,"timeElapsed":363035},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6620,"timeElapsed":369659},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":12063,"timeElapsed":381727},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":72785,"timeElapsed":464245},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679249533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8383,"timeElapsed":472633},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679259164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":9625,"timeElapsed":482263},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":9319,"timeElapsed":491589},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6502,"timeElapsed":498097},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3486,"timeElapsed":501588},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6062,"timeElapsed":507653},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4499,"timeElapsed":512157},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679295983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":6921,"timeElapsed":519083},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679332863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":34973,"timeElapsed":555963},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679354401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":21533,"timeElapsed":577501},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7361,"timeElapsed":584867},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679370098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8326,"timeElapsed":593198},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679376967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":6867,"timeElapsed":600067},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4469,"timeElapsed":604541},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679393811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":12364,"timeElapsed":616910},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679400649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6834,"timeElapsed":623749},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":628037},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679478675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":72318,"timeElapsed":701775},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679483515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4835,"timeElapsed":706615},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679493748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10227,"timeElapsed":716848},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679503531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9777,"timeElapsed":726631},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679512535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8999,"timeElapsed":735635},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679520441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7901,"timeElapsed":743541},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679525532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5085,"timeElapsed":748631},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679535437,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9901,"timeElapsed":758537},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6499,"timeElapsed":765041},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679549579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7633,"timeElapsed":772679},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679569728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":18351,"timeElapsed":792828},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679576127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6393,"timeElapsed":799227},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679589679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":13546,"timeElapsed":812779},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679597127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7443,"timeElapsed":820227},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679608297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":11165,"timeElapsed":831397},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679616225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7925,"timeElapsed":839325},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4777,"timeElapsed":844107},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679623789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2776,"timeElapsed":846889},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679632859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9065,"timeElapsed":855959},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679646386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11407,"timeElapsed":869486},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679654644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":8253,"timeElapsed":877743},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679660611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5962,"timeElapsed":883711},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679699178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":38561,"timeElapsed":922278},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5887,"timeElapsed":928169},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679713477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8402,"timeElapsed":936576},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679716148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2669,"timeElapsed":939248},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679718061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1909,"timeElapsed":941161},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679724994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6928,"timeElapsed":948094},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679737273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":10859,"timeElapsed":960373},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679744283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7005,"timeElapsed":967383},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679750869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":6581,"timeElapsed":973969},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679752721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":975821},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679760181,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7455,"timeElapsed":983281},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679766015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5829,"timeElapsed":989115},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679771765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5745,"timeElapsed":994865},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679775234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3464,"timeElapsed":998334},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679777517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2280,"timeElapsed":1000617},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679782027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4505,"timeElapsed":1005127},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679793595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":10335,"timeElapsed":1016695},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679799797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6197,"timeElapsed":1022897},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679806728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6926,"timeElapsed":1029828},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679809571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2841,"timeElapsed":1032671},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679814597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5021,"timeElapsed":1037697},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679817626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":1040725},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679820823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3193,"timeElapsed":1043923},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679822867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":1045967},{"subjectID":"5taaxwp8za","prolificID":"605776c7ffd8cb64476fc73f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b25a27970e0fcd674f7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679829175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6303,"timeElapsed":1052274}]